I say I say Prue yeah HDFC life qk is a
safe room already Trimble move again
Donna my serger Ixtapa trade lane our
the Kiska structured better LeBron the
key I think dunno taste of just coffee
Milton in fact the juicer except the
petitioner here both sides are
definitely you know Adam of purify you
know broader structure they K to middle
area per shift in life may a be B plus a
potential better in fact just the Rica
see if sequence whenever arched or just
swing by around 459 chaos but I think
you know coffee important a 460k
stop-loss gives up a gypsy life my ape
trading all be initiate yeah just after
one lower target poke around 5:30 for
chaos Moscow I think if you undertake
furniture you replaced it so I think we
have a gypsy life make fresh straightly
adjust attacks
yeah I guess if you already use of
coffee chalupa has its maybe structure
almost similar here but magellanic a
whopper who was I hurdle here around 390
Casper Jesse go particular level breakup
I think of the momentum equally miss of
that but salon law or trade kill us a
much leverage every life make but
portion here and no fresh top of the
other
[Music]